<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Chronicles on Boricua D&amp;D GM</title><link>https://boricuadndgm.github.io/boricuadndgm/tags/chronicles/</link><description>Recent content in Chronicles on Boricua D&amp;D GM</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>boricuadndgm</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 12:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://boricuadndgm.github.io/boricuadndgm/tags/chronicles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Adventure Chronicle - Session 1: Mine Cleanup Crew</title><link>https://boricuadndgm.github.io/boricuadndgm/posts/chronicles/session1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 12:00:00 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://boricuadndgm.github.io/boricuadndgm/posts/chronicles/session1/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="session-1-recap"&gt;Session 1 Recap
&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Met &lt;strong&gt;Gordon&lt;/strong&gt;, Assistant (to the) Regional Manager, &lt;strong&gt;Acquisitions, Inc&lt;/strong&gt;. Gordon acted as a welcome party and introduced you to the town council members looking to hire adventurers. Gordon is determined to help the party set up a franchise at all costs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Met &lt;strong&gt;Marinella&lt;/strong&gt; town council members &lt;strong&gt;Eva&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Elias&lt;/strong&gt; who hired you to rid the local mine from a recent monster infestation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eva secretly requested the party to find evidence of wrongdoing by the &lt;strong&gt;TMM corporation&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Met &lt;strong&gt;Sigrid&lt;/strong&gt; head of mining operations for TMM. Her main concern is to ensure miner safety and that the mines continue to operate as it is the livelihood of many locals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interviewing Sigrid reveals that a recent mystery shipment coincides with the appearance of monsters in the mine. The monsters appear to be grotesque versions of normal beasts and are not sentient but highly ferocious.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Alicia&lt;/strong&gt; uncovered that at least one miner has died and others have been injured. Other miners have confirmed that weird things have been happening like people having headaches, hearing voices, and some suspect the food and water.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Theo&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Cesar&lt;/strong&gt; investigated the water from the well which contained some weird dark tar-like substance. When the substance made contact with grass it began to wither.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kairos&lt;/strong&gt; cleverly made contact with “Jay” , a suspicious character from corporate offices that has lost a ledger. “Jay” seems worried about the consequences with the corporation. A deal was struck to have the party retrieve the manifest in one of the break rooms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The party has entered the mine and so far have noticed the withering mushrooms that are meant to clean the air from hazardous gasses. In the next session, the party will begin investigating the -1F sub level.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id="npc-encountered"&gt;NPC Encountered
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gordon Flanders, human elf assistant, local contact and facilitator&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id="town-council"&gt;Town Council
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eva Pescatore, female human, senior member of the Consiglio Maggiore&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Elias Feuerberger, male human member of the Consiglio Maggiore&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id="tmm"&gt;TMM
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sigrid Gustafsdotter, Head of Mining Operations, female dwarf, hired adventurers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leer, female dragonborn miner, revealed details about suspicious recent events, injuries, and death&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Andres, male elf miner, see &lt;em&gt;Return Basement Key&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;“Jay”, human male corporate administrator, see &lt;em&gt;Retrieve the Ledger&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hanz, human male corporate private security, unhelpful&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bogomir (Bog), blacksmith, no contact yet&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>Adventure Chronicle - Session 2: Mine Cleanup Crew</title><link>https://boricuadndgm.github.io/boricuadndgm/posts/chronicles/session2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 12:00:00 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://boricuadndgm.github.io/boricuadndgm/posts/chronicles/session2/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="session-2-recap"&gt;Session 2 Recap
&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Descent into the Corrupted Mine&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mine Cleanup and Initial Findings&lt;/strong&gt;:
The party successfully cleared the first level (-1F) of the mine, eliminating all monsters near the surface.
After their battle, they returned to the mining camp to rest and report their findings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mutated Beasts and Strange Effects&lt;/strong&gt;:
While navigating the mine, the party encountered grotesque, mutated versions of typical creatures warped with tumors and boils.
The creatures emitted a foul smell to match their appearance.
The deeper the party ventured, the more they felt strange side effects creeping in, affecting their senses.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Adventure Quest Log - Mine Cleanup Crew</title><link>https://boricuadndgm.github.io/boricuadndgm/posts/chronicles/quests/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 12:00:00 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://boricuadndgm.github.io/boricuadndgm/posts/chronicles/quests/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="quest-log"&gt;Quest Log
&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;h2 id="starting-a-business"&gt;Starting a Business
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Acquisitions, Inc&lt;/strong&gt; has accepted your application to intern with the company. Your assignment is to set up operations for a franchise in the town of Marinella.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Given by&lt;/strong&gt;: Gordon&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reward&lt;/strong&gt;: Business location and a means to make money.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time to Completion:&lt;/strong&gt; Weeks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id="monsters-in-the-mine"&gt;Monsters in the Mine
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;TMM&lt;/strong&gt; company and &lt;strong&gt;Marinella&lt;/strong&gt; council hired your guild to help address a monster infestation in the local mine.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>